威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们将要创建一个很棒的函数，但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We are going to
create I use a great function, but
我们称这个对象为单拷贝或单拷贝，我甚至不想要我们的副本
we call this object single copies or
single, I don't even want us a copy of
这首歌不是我们每个功能的同一个版本。
that song is no single same
version of each of our functions.
我们将运行 i use a creative function，它将创建对象
And we're going to run I use a creative
function, it's going to create objects
内部使用对象创建，这只是创建对象的另一种方式
inside using object create, which is just
another way of creating the object.dddd
但是这些对象以某种方式与用户函数存储对象有联系。
But that objects going to have somehow our
bond to that user function store object.
这意味着，当该对象返回到用户 one 时,
Meaning that, when that object gets
returned out into user one with
它的属性，但没有任何功能存储在里面。
its properties, but
no function stored on it.
当我们最终使用这个对象时，使用一个点增量，它不会找到
When we end up using that object, using
one dot increment, and it doesn't find
对象的增量，我们会惊慌吗? 它会以某种方式链接到
increment on the object, are we gonna
panic It's gonna have a link somehow to
使用一个函数存储，它会找到递增方法并使用它。
use a function store where it's gonna
find the increment method and use it.
好了，各位，我们开始吧。
All right people, here we go.
一号线。
Line one.
杰夫，我们在全球记忆中做什么？
Jeff, what are we doing in global memory?
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
Jeff: 我们正在声明一个用户创建的函数。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: We are declaring
a function user created.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 非常好，在全局内存中，用户,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Excellent,
in global memory, user,
创造者，威尔 · 森塔斯: 就是这样。
creator,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There it is.
旧功能，非常好。
The old function, excellent.
现在，为马特干杯。
Now, to Matt.
Matt: 我们要定义一个常量用户函数存储库-
&gt;&gt; Matt: We're gonna define
a constant user function store-
威尔 · 森特斯: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah.
杰夫: 带有一个值 Will Sentance: Of a object。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: With a value
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Of an object.
马特: 关于一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Matt: Of an object.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，不要被抓住,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
don't get caught people,
在这里，认为它是其他的东西。
here in thinking it's anything else.
是一个物体，没错。
It's an object, yeah.
就是这个。
There it is.
是的，那个东西上面储存了什么？
Yeah, and what's stored on the object?
Matt: 我们有一个增量属性和一个登录属性。
&gt;&gt; Matt: We have an increment property and
a login property.
Will Sentance: 是的，这是一个递增方法，因为函数是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, and that's
an increment method because the function's
储存在里面。
stored on it.
和一个登录属性，这也是一个方法。
And a login Property
which is also a method.
我的胳膊开始疼了。
Well, my arm is actually starting to ache.
好了。
There we go.
没问题。
No problem.
就是这个。
There it is.
非常感谢。
Thank you too much.
现在我们进入下一张幻灯片的左边。
Now we move on to the next
slide left hand side.
布莱登，该怎么办？
Braden, what to say to do?
Braden: 声明常量 user-1。
&gt;&gt; Braden: Declare the constant user-1.
杰夫: 用户 -1。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: User-1.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们知道这里显示的是什么吗，同志们。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Do we know
what it showing here, people.
不，我们要去创造我们，全新的每一个人。
Nope, we got to go and
run us the creator, brand new everybody.
学生: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Students: Execution context.
威尔 · 句子: 执行上下文，美丽。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
beautiful.
这是如此充满活力，以通过我们的
That was so vibrant in which to pass our
争论将和三个全新的执行
arguments will and
three brand new execution
威尔 · 森塔斯: 所以
context as you all said
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So
好极了，就是这个。
wonderfully, here it is.
不，就是这个。
No, there it is.
好了，我们开始吧
Okay, into it we
杰夫: 我
go,
&gt;&gt; Jeff: I
没有做的是本地记忆我们有，杰夫: 好吧,
didn't do is local memory we had,
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Okay,
我们要做的第一件事，交给 Dan，我们要先做什么？
first thing we handle, over to Dan,
what are we gonna handle first?
Will Sentance: 我们将 Will 分配给参数名。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We assign
Will to the argument name.
杰夫: 差不多，威尔对-威尔 · 森塔斯的论点是: 对不起,
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Almost, the Will argument to the-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Sorry,
参数名。
to the parameter name.
杰夫: 参数名，是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Parameter name, yeah, exactly.
然后下一个参数是 score，我们用什么参数分配？
And then the next parameter is score,
we assign in what argument?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 3。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 3.
杰夫: 3，漂亮。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: 3, beautiful.
很好，谢谢你，丹。
Very nice, thank you Dan.
现在我们进入函数体，这个函数的整个点
Now we enter the body of the function
where the whole point of this function
顺便说一下，使用存储在其中的特定用户的数据创建一个对象
by the way, create an object with the data
of a particular user stored in it and
这个功能永远，永远不会被应用到特定的用户身上。
the functionality that will ever,
ever be applied to that particular user.
这是唯一的一点。
That's the only point.
那么下一行我们要做什么呢？
So what do we do in the next line?
凯拉，我们创造一个？
Kyla, we create a?
一个经常使用的新用户。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A constant new user.
杰夫: 是的，并赋予它将句子: 空对象。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yeah, and assign to it
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Empty object.
杰夫: 一个空物体。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: An empty object.
继续，对不起。
Go ahead, sorry.
Will Sentance: 具有用户功能存储属性。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: With the properties
of user function store.
杰夫: 没有属性，它实际上是一个空对象。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: No properties,
it's really an empty object.
但是我会说我同意，不知怎么的
But I will say I do agree, it somehow got
这个物体之间的亲密联系
an intimate link between
this object that's
我使用函数存储。
being created And
I use the function store.
我们还不知道如何，但有一个亲密的联系。
We do not yet know how but
there is a intimate link.
好吧，让我们来试试这些特性。
Okay, but
let's get fitting in those properties.
Dan 实际上 Adam 刚才的事很抱歉。
Dan, actually, Adam, sorry about there.
我不应该总是在后面指定它，亚当。
I should not always specify
it at the back, Adam.
继续。
Go ahead.
我们得到了一个新的用户对象。
We've got a new user object.
我们要立即增加什么内容？
What are we adding immediately to it?
Will Sentance: 一个名为 name 的属性。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: A property called name.
杰夫: 是的，然后呢？
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yeah, and?
Will Sentance: 并重新分配参数名的值，即 Will。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And reassigning its
value of the argument name, which is Will.
杰夫: 好极了，然后呢？
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Fantastic yeah, and then?
威尔 · 森坦斯: 分数是3？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The score is 3?
杰夫: 是的，很好，那个物体。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yeah, perfect okay, that object.
我们怎么处理它？
What do we do with it?
看起来我们需要的。
It's kind of seems that what we need.
它获得了数据，并以某种方式与我们的功能相连接，但是
It's got the data and
it linked somehow to our functions, but
它被困在我们的行刑环境里了。
it's stuck inside our execution context.
马特，我们怎么把它弄出来。
Matt, how we get it out.
我们要把这个物体完全返回到全局标签 Matt 中,
We're going to return the object exactly
out into what global label Matt,
用一个神奇的。
use one fantastic.
就是这个名字: 威尔,
And there it is with name: Will,
配乐: [声音]3。
score: [SOUND] 3.
上面有增量方法吗？
And any increment method on it?
没错，但它确实和这里的函数集有某种联系。
Exactly, but it does have somehow a link
To this collection of functions up here.
过一会儿就知道了，别担心。
We'll see how in a moment, don't worry.
好了，我们回到全球，我们现在宣布用户2。
Okay, we're back out in global
we declare now user two.
它将是另一个调用用户的结果，另一个运行,
It's going to be the result of
another call to user, another running,
用于运行用户创建器的另一个执行上下文。
another execution context for
the running of user creator.
这次是提姆的争论，还有五个。
This time with the argument of Tim,
and five.
它的输出是什么？
What would it's output be?
我就跳过执行上下文吧,
I'm just gonna sort of skip
the execution context,
知道我们已经走进去，做了一切。
know that we've gone inside and done all.
那我们最后会怎么样呢 Matt,
So what are we gonna end up with here,
Matt,
存储到用户2B 中的所有输出？
all the output that gets
stored into user 2B?
Will Sentance: 属性名为 Tim 值的对象。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The object with
the property name to the value of Tim.
这就是它的属性，值为5的分数，以及一个不可磨灭的链接。
That does it property, score of
the value 5, and an indelible link.
杰夫: 是啊，一种神秘的不可磨灭的联系，贯穿到？
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yeah,
a mysterious indelible link, through to?
Will Sentance: 用户函数存储。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The user function store.
杰夫: 通过用户功能存储。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Through to
the user function store.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 看，他们合并得很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Look at that,
they merged well, there.
并且您可以通过用户函数存储。
And you are through to
the user function store.
好了，现在我们检查一下。
Okay, now we do our check.
我们要做的是，让我们做 user1.increment,
We're gonna do, let's do user1.increment,
这就是我在这里得到的，user1.increment。
it's what I've got up here,
user1.increment.
托德，你已经知道了，该你上场了。
Todd, you already know, it's over to you.
托德，JavaScript 要去哪里寻找 user1呢？
Todd, where's JavaScript
gonna go looking for user1?
杰夫: 在全球的记忆里。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: In the global memory.
全局记忆，我们找到它了吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global memory,
we find it?
杰夫: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yes.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 是的，我们知道，等等。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes we do, hold on.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 是的，我们知道。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes we do.
我们在那个物体上寻找什么？
What are we looking for on that object?
杰夫: Increment。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Increment.
句子: 增量，我们找到了吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Increment,
do we find it?
杰夫: 不是马上。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Not immediately.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 不，不在那个物体上。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No,
it's not on that object.
我们要放弃吗？
Do we give up?
杰夫: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: No.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们跟随紫色到哪里去？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Where
do we follow the purple?
杰夫: 不可磨灭的纽带。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: The indelible link.
威尔 · 森特斯: 不可磨灭的纽带，直到？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The indelible link,
up to?
杰夫: 用户功能。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: User function.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 功能偷了我们在它上面找到的地方-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Function
stole where we find on it-
杰夫: Increment。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Increment.
Will Sentance: Increment，我们获取它的代码。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Increment,
and we grab its code.
我们马上就要开始处决的人。
And people we're gonna start
executing in a moment.
我希望你们能看到一些，关于这个函数的有趣的东西，我们需要
So I want you all to see some interesting
things about that function that we need to
确保是真的。
make sure are true.
因为这个函数可以用在用户1，用户2，用户400上。
Because that function is gonna be able to
be used on user 1, on user 2, on user 400.
在我们这样做之前，让我们先了解一下这个链接实际上是如何存储的。
Before we do that though, let's understand
how this link is actually stored.
它是使用 auto.create 制作的。
It's made using auto.create.
无论你经历了什么，我们都会得到那种不可磨灭的联系，那种联系。
Whatever you pass in,
we get that indelible link, that bond.
它是如何存储的，对象，重拍,
How is it stored, the object, the reshoot,
create 确实创建了一个空对象，我支持这一点。
object.create does create an empty object,
I stand by that.
Kayla 在暗示这个链接是怎么建立起来的？
And Kayla was hinting,
well hold on how is this link made?
她这么说是对的，这是事实。
Well she is right to say that,
is something that happens.
但是在引擎盖下面我们看不到它。
But it's under the hood
that we can't see it.
当我们来安慰你的时候，我马上就告诉你怎么做。
When we come to console I'll
show you how in a second.
此对象上的隐藏属性。
A hidden property on this object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这是一个有趣的问题，它是双下划线,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And it's a funny one,
it's double underscore,
原型双下划线，他们称之为 dunderline proto
proto double underscore,
they call that dunderscore proto or
原型 dunder 原型 dunder 原型财产,
dunder, proto dunder, the proto property,
存储在里面，或者链接到。
and it has stored in it or link to.
用户功能存储。
User function store.
不不不。
No, no, no, no.
将该对象返回给用户1，并
Returns that object into user 1, and
在幕后，它仍然有它的
behind the scenes, it still has its
原型链接到用户功能存储器。
proto link up to user function store.
这个原型链接，这个链接从用户1到用户函数存储。
This proto link, this chain connection
from user 1 up to user function store.
这里也有。
And it's also on here.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们有一个参照物，一个链接,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We have a referent,
a link,
真正能看到的字体。
would actually literally
see written in here.
用户函数存储，指向该对象的链接。
User function store,
a link to that object.
意思是，我们开始吧，布莱登。
Meaning, let's start, Braden.
如果我在做 user1.increment，请告诉我。
Braden, if I were doing user1.increment,
talk me through.
我在哪里寻找用户1？
Where do I look for user one?
我们会找到它吗？
Would we find it?
杰夫: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Yes.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我知道。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, I do.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这个不起作用，]我发现是的，我发现了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This one is not
working,] I find it yes, I do.
我在它上面寻找增量方法。
I look for the increment method on it.
我找到了吗？
Do I find it?
杰夫: 不是现在。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Not right away.
是的，但是 JavaScript 是做什么的呢？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, but
what does JavaScript do?
实际上我正要告诉你们 JavaScript 有它的非凡之处,
I was actually gonna tell you,
JavaScript has its quite remarkable,
原型特征。
prototypal feature.
这意味着当它找不到对象 a 给定的属性时,
That means when it does not find
on the object A given property,
方法或数据，它不恐慌。
method or data it does not panic.
相反，它直接进入了原始属性不是的状态
Instead it goes straight to
the __proto__ property not to be
和原型混淆了。
confused with prototype.
你知道这是不对的。
You see that is wrong.
所以它是原始财产，它关注与什么相联系,
So it's the __proto__ property and
it looks at what is linking to,
连接到原型链上,
and is linking to the proto
Up the prototype chain,
但是，是的，在原型链上，这是可以的措辞。
but yeah, up the prototype
chain that's okay phrasing.
向上的原型链或
Up the prototype chain or
让我们通过它的原始引用链接到布拉登。
let's say through its proto-reference
link up to where Bradon.
Jeff: 用户函数-Will Sentance: 用户函数存储。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: The user function-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The user function store.
我们发现了什么？
What do we find?
杰夫: Increment。
&gt;&gt; Jeff: Increment.
Will Sentance: Increment method，And we grab it And
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Increment method,
and we grab it And
我们为它的代码创建一个全新的执行环境。
we create a brand new execution
context for its code.
我一会儿再说这个。
I'm gonna come to that in a moment.
但是现在让我们先来看看这个模型,
But for now let's have thumbs
on this model where look people,
这不是很美吗？
ain't this beautiful?
这个用户1，这个用户2。
This user 1, this user 2.
他们都没有我们功能的单独副本
Neither of them have individual copies
of our functions it would be totally
冗余是对记忆空间的浪费。
redundant as a waste of memory space.
我们真的很擅长解决问题。
We really good at a problem.
这些代码被保存在内存中，并且作为浪费的内存空间被复制。
That code is saved in memory and
copies of it as it's wasted memory space.
相反，我们通过亲到隐藏的财产或
Instead we have through
the pro to hidden property or
链接到一个拷贝或者一个对象
link up to a single copy or
up to a single object where all those
我们希望所有这些对象都能访问的函数被存储。
functions we want all these
objects have access to are stored.
这是 JavaScript 的原型本质，当我们查看它们的时候，它们是对象
And it's JavaScript prototype nature
that objects when we look on them for
我们不会放弃，也不会找到。
a method we don't give up and
we don't find it.
我们首先检查原始属性，然后前往那个对象。
We first go check the proto property and
head up to that object.
也就是说它的原型是一个特征就是一个特征就像它的词法范围一样
That is its prototype was one of features
is a feature like its lexical scope
属性是它的全局存储器的一个特征。
property is a feature
like its global memory.
就像它是一个功能一样。
Like it's a feature.
这是一个特性，如果我们设置对象，它们就会与其他对象建立连接
It's a feature that objects have a
connection to other objects if we set them
通过他们的原始财产来实现。
to do so through their proto property.
当 JavaScript 点击查找某个对象而对象没有找到它时,
And when JavaScript hits looking for
something and the object doesn't find it,
它马上就会出错。
it does an error immediately.
它去检查一层或更多层。
It goes and checks one layer up or
maybe more.
我们一会儿就知道了。
We'll see in a moment.